<a href=https://github.com/hlais/Kata---a---Day><b>Back to README</b><a>

Day #80: 

Difficulty: 6 kyu

Solved: Friday, March 30th, 2018


There is an array with some numbers. All numbers are equal except for one. Try to find it!

findUniq([ 1, 1, 1, 2, 1, 1 ]) === 2
findUniq([ 0, 0, 0.55, 0, 0 ]) === 0.55
It’s guaranteed that array contains more than 3 numbers.

The tests contain some very huge arrays, so think about performance.

This is the first kata in series:

Find the unique number (this kata)
Find the unique string
Find The Unique