<a href=https://github.com/hlais/Kata---a---Day><b>Back to README</b><a>

Day #156: 

* <b>Difficulty:</b> 7 kyu

* <b>Solution Class:</b> [Predict Your Age](Calculator.cs)

* <b>Solved:</b> Thursday, July 26<sup>th</sup>, 2018

Details:

My grandfather always predicted how old people would get, and right before he passed away he revealed his secret!

In honor of my grandfather's memory we will write a function using his formula!

Take a list of ages when each of your great-grandparent died.
Multiply each number by itself.
Add them all together.
Take the square root of the result.
Divide by two.
Example
predictAge(65, 60, 75, 55, 60, 63, 64, 45) == 86
Note: the result should be rounded down to the nearest integer.

Some random tests might fail due to a bug in the JavaScript implementation. Simply resubmit if that happens to you.