<a href=https://github.com/hlais/Kata---a---Day><b>Back to README</b><a>

Day #84: 

Difficulty: 6 kyu

Solved: Tuesday, April 10th, 2018


I love Fibonacci numbers in general, but I must admit I love some more than others.

I would like for you to write me a function that when given a number (n) returns the n-th number in the Fibonacci Sequence.

For example:

   NthFib(4) == 2
Because 2 is the 4th number in the Fibonacci Sequence.

For reference, the first two numbers in the Fibonacci sequence are 0 and 1, and each subsequent number is the sum of the previous two.