<a href=https://github.com/hlais/Kata---a---Day><b>Back to README</b><a>

Day #93: 

Difficulty: 6 kyu

Solved: Friday, April 20th, 2018

Complete the method so that it formats the words into a single comma separated value. The last word should be separated by the word 'and' instead of a comma. The method takes in an array of strings and returns a single formatted string. Empty string values should be ignored. Empty arrays or null/nil values being passed into the method should result in an empty string being returned.

Kata.FormatWords(new string[] {"ninja", "samurai", "ronin"}) => "ninja, samurai and ronin"
Kata.FormatWords(new string[] {"ninja", "", "ronin"}) => "ninja and ronin"
Kata.FormatWords(new string[] {}) => ""