<a href=https://github.com/hlais/Kata---a---Day><b>Back to README</b><a>

Day #110: 

* <b>Difficulty:</b>5 kyu

* <b>Solution Class:</b> [Integers: Recreation One](Tic-Tac-Toe%20Checker.cs)

* <b>Solved:</b> Thursday, May 17<sup>th</sup>, 2018

Divisors of 42 are : 1, 2, 3, 6, 7, 14, 21, 42. These divisors squared are: 1, 4, 9, 36, 49, 196, 441, 1764. The sum of the squared divisors is 2500 which is 50 * 50, a square!

Given two integers m, n (1 <= m <= n) we want to find all integers between m and n whose sum of squared divisors is itself a square. 42 is such a number.

The result will be an array of arrays or of tuples (in C an array of Pair) or a string, each subarray having two elements, first the number whose squared divisors is a square and then the sum of the squared divisors.

#Examples:

list_squared(1, 250) --> [[1, 1], [42, 2500], [246, 84100]]
list_squared(42, 250) --> [[42, 2500], [246, 84100]]
The form of the examples may change according to the language, see Example Tests: for more details.

Note

In Fortran - as in any other language - the returned string is not permitted to contain any redundant trailing whitespace: you can use dynamically allocated character strings.