<a href=https://github.com/hlais/Kata---a---Day><b>Back to README</b><a>

Day #97: 

Difficulty: 5 kyu

Solved: Wenesday, April 25th, 2018

If we were to set up a Tic-Tac-Toe game, we would want to know whether the board's current state is solved, wouldn't we? Our goal is to create a function that will check that for us!

Assume that the board comes in the form of a 3x3 array, where the value is 0 if a spot is empty, 1 if it is an "X", or 2 if it is an "O", like so:

[[0, 0, 1],
 [0, 1, 2],
 [2, 1, 0]]
We want our function to return:

-1 if the board is not yet finished (there are empty spots),
1 if "X" won,
2 if "O" won,
0 if it's a cat's game (i.e. a draw).
You may assume that the board passed in is valid in the context of a game of Tic-Tac-Toe.