<a href=https://github.com/hlais/Kata---a---Day><b>Back to README</b><a>

Day #4: 

Difficulty: 7 kyu

Solved: Saturday, January 13th, 2018

Description:

Jenny has written a function that returns a greeting for a user. However, she's in love with Johnny, and would like to greet him slightly different. She added a special case to her function, but she made a mistake.

Can you help her?

