<a href=https://github.com/hlais/Kata---a---Day><b>Back to README</b><a>

Day #72: 

Difficulty: 6 kyu

Solved: Thursday, March 22th, 2018

In this Kata, you will implement the Luhn Algorithm, which is used to help validate credit card numbers.

Given a positive integer of up to 16 digits, return true if it is a valid credit card number, and false if it is not.

Here is the algorithm:

Double every other digit, scanning from right to left, starting from the second digit (from the right).

Another way to think about it is: if there are an even number of digits, double every other digit starting with the first; if there are an odd number of digits, double every other digit starting with the second:

1714 ==> [1*, 7, 1*, 4] ==> [2, 7, 2, 4]

12345 ==> [1, 2*, 3, 4*, 5] ==> [1, 4, 3, 8, 5]

891 ==> [8, 9*, 1] ==> [8, 18, 1]
If a resulting number is greater than 9, replace it with the sum of its own digits (which is the same as subtracting 9 from it):

[8, 18*, 1] ==> [8, (1+8), 1] ==> [8, 9, 1]

or:

[8, 18*, 1] ==> [8, (18-9), 1] ==> [8, 9, 1]
Sum all of the final digits:

[8, 9, 1] ==> 8 + 9 + 1 = 18
Finally, take that sum and divide it by 10. If the remainder equals zero, the original credit card number is valid.

  18 (modulus) 10 ==> 8 , which is not equal to 0, so this is not a valid credit card number
For F# and C# users:

The input will be a string of spaces and digits 0..9