<a href=https://github.com/hlais/Kata---a---Day><b>Back to README</b><a>

Day #135: 

* <b>Difficulty:</b> 8 kyu

* <b>Solution Class:</b> [Correct Mistake](Growth%20of%20a%20Population.cs)

* <b>Solved:</b> Sunday, June 17<sup>th</sup>, 2018

Details:

Character recognition software is widely used to digitise printed texts. Thus the texts can be edited, searched and stored on a computer.

When documents (especially pretty old ones written with a typewriter), are digitised character recognition softwares often make mistakes.

Your task is correct the errors in the digitised text. You only have to handle the following mistakes:

S is misinterpreted as 5
O is misinterpreted as 0
I is misinterpreted as 1
The test cases contain numbers only by mistake.