<a href=https://github.com/hlais/Kata---a---Day><b>Back to README</b><a>

Day #159: 

* <b>Difficulty:</b> 7 kyu

* <b>Solution Class:</b> [Google Interview Question](UnluckyDays.cs)

* <b>Solved:</b> Thursday, August 23<sup>rd</sup>, 2018

Details:

If I give you a name of a city as a string, I want you to return a string that shows how many times each letter shows up in the string by using an asterisk *

SEE TEST CASE!

As you can see for Chicago, in the return string, I only show the letter "c" once even though there are 2 "c" in Chicago (regardless of upper or lowercase).

I show 2 asteriks since there are 2 "c" in Chicago.

In the return string there are no spaces between the letters, asteriks, and commas.

GetStrings("Chicago") => "c:**,h:*,i:*,a:*,g:*,o:*"
Note that the return string contains the characters in order of first appearence in the original string.