<a href=https://github.com/hlais/Kata---a---Day><b>Back to README</b><a>

Day #112: 

* <b>Difficulty:</b>6 kyu

* <b>Solution Class:</b> [Checking Groups](Tic-Tac-Toe%20Checker.cs)

* <b>Solved:</b> Monday, May 21<sup>th</sup>, 2018

In English and programming, groups can be made using symbols such as () and {} that change meaning. However, these groups must be closed in the correct order to maintain correct syntax.

Your job in this kata will be to make a program that checks a string for correct grouping. For instance, the following groups are done correctly:

({})
[[]()]
[{()}]
The next are done incorrectly:

{(})
([]
[])
A correct string cannot close groups in the wrong order, open a group but fail to close it, or close a group before it is opened.

Your function will take an input string that may contain any of the symbols (), {} or [] to create groups.

It should return True if the string is empty or otherwise grouped correctly, or False if it is grouped incorrectly.