<a href=https://github.com/hlais/Kata---a---Day><b>Back to README</b><a>

Day #61: 

Difficulty: 5 kyu

Solved: Sunday, March 11th, 2018

In the following 6 digit number:

283910
91 is the greatest sequence of 2 digits.

In the following 10 digit number:

1234567890
67890 is the greatest sequence of 5 digits.

Complete the solution so that it returns the largest five digit number found within the number given. The number will be passed in as a string of only digits. It should return a five digit integer. The number passed may be as large as 1000 digits.

Adapted from ProjectEuler.net