<a href=https://github.com/hlais/Kata---a---Day><b>Back to README</b><a>

Day #28: 

Difficulty: 7 kyu

Solved: Tuesday, February 6th, 2018

Description:

A square of squares
You like building blocks. You especially like building blocks that are squares. And what you even like more, is to arrange them into a square of square building blocks!

However, sometimes, you can't arrange them into a square. Instead, you end up with an ordinary rectangle! Those blasted things! If you just had a way to know, whether you're currently working in vain… Wait! That's it! You just have to check if your number of building blocks is a perfect square.

Task
Given an integral number, determine if it's a square number:

In mathematics, a square number or perfect square is an integer that is the square of an integer; in other words, it is the product of some integer with itself.

The tests will always use some integral number, so don't worry about that in dynamic typed languages.

Examples
Kata.isSquare(-1) // => false
Kata.isSquare( 3) // => false
Kata.isSquare( 4) // => true
Kata.isSquare(25) // => true
Kata.isSquare(26) // => false