<a href=https://github.com/hlais/Kata---a---Day><b>Back to README</b><a>

Day #161: 

* <b>Difficulty:</b> 7 kyu

* <b>Solution Class:</b> [Is Leap Year](LeapYears.cs)

* <b>Solved:</b> Friday, August 24<sup>th</sup>, 2018

Details:

In this kata you should simply determine, whether a given year is a leap year or not. In case you don't know the rules, here they are:

years divisible by 4 are leap years
but years divisible by 100 are no leap years
but years divisible by 400 are leap years
Additional Notes:

Only valid years (positive integers) will be tested, so you don't have to validate them
Examples can be found in the test fixture.