<a href=https://github.com/hlais/Kata---a---Day><b>Back to README</b><a>

Day #148: 

* <b>Difficulty:</b> 8 kyu

* <b>Solution Class:</b> [Object Oriented Piracy](Calculator.cs)

* <b>Solved:</b> Saturday, July 7<sup>th</sup>, 2018

Details:

You are a leader of a small pirate crew. And you have a plan. With the help of OOP you wish to make a pretty efficient system to identify ships with a heavy booty on board.

Unfortunattely for you, people weigh a lot this days, so how do you know if a ship if full of gold and not people?

You begin with writing a generic Ship class:

public class Ship
{
  public int Draft;
  public int Crew;

  public Ship(int draft, int crew)
  {
    Draft = draft;
    Crew = crew;
  }
}
Every time your spies see a new ship enter the dock, they will create a new ship object based on their observations:

draft - an estimate of the ship's weight based on how low it is in the water
crew - the count of crew on board
Ship titanic = new Ship(15, 10);
Taking into account that an average crew member on board adds 1.5 units to the draft, a ship that has a draft of more than 20 without crew is considered worthy to loot. Any ship weighing that much must have a lot of booty!

Add the method

IsWorthIt
to decide if the ship is worthy to loot. For example:

titanic.IsWorthIt() => false