<a href=https://github.com/hlais/Kata---a---Day><b>Back to README</b><a>

Day #171: 

* <b>Difficulty:</b> 8 kyu

* <b>Solution Class:</b> [Do I get a bonus?](DoIGetBonus.cs)

* <b>Solved:</b> Saturday, September 29 <sup>th</sup>, 2018

Details:

It's bonus time in the big city! The fatcats are rubbing their paws in anticipation... but who is going to make the most money?

Build a function that takes in two arguments (salary, bonus). Salary will be an integer, and bonus a boolean.

If bonus is true, the salary should be multiplied by 10. If bonus is false, the fatcat did not make enough money and must receive only his stated salary.