<a href=https://github.com/hlais/Kata---a---Day><b>Back to README</b><a>

Day #157: 

* <b>Difficulty:</b> 7 kyu

* <b>Solution Class:</b> [Covfefe](Calculator.cs)

* <b>Solved:</b> Mondayy, July 30<sup>th</sup>, 2018

Details:

Your are given a string. You must replace the word(s) coverage by covfefe, however, if you don't find the word coverage in the string, you must add covfefe at the end of the string with a leading space.

For the languages where the string is not immutable (such as ruby), don't modify the given string, otherwise this will break the test cases.