<a href=https://github.com/hlais/Kata---a---Day><b>Back to README</b><a>

Day #18: 

Difficulty: 8 kyu

Solved: Saturday , January 27th, 2018

Description:

Create a function which answers the question "Are you playing banjo?".
If your name starts with the letter "R" or lower case "r", you are playing banjo!

The function takes a name as its only argument, and returns one of the following strings:

name + " plays banjo" 
name + " does not play banjo"
Names given are always valid strings.

