<a href=https://github.com/hlais/Kata---a---Day><b>Back to README</b><a>

Day #40: 

Difficulty: 6 kyu

Solved: Sunday, February 18th, 2018

Description:
In this kata, you must create a digital root function.

A digital root is the recursive sum of all the digits in a number. Given n, take the sum of the digits of n. If that value has two digits, continue reducing in this way until a single-digit number is produced. This is only applicable to the natural numbers.

Here's how it works (Ruby example given):