<a href=https://github.com/hlais/Kata---a---Day><b>Back to README</b><a>

Day #137: 

* <b>Difficulty:</b> 3 kyu

* <b>Solution Class:</b> [Calculator](Calculator.cs)

* <b>Solved:</b> Tuesday, June 19<sup>th</sup>, 2018

Details:

Create a simple calculator that given a string of operators (+ - * and /) and numbers separated by spaces returns the value of that expression

Example:

Calculator().evaluate("2 / 2 + 3 * 4 - 6") # => 7
Remember about the order of operations! Multiplications and divisions have a higher priority and should be performed left-to-right. Additions and subtractions have a lower priority and should also be performed left-to-right.