<a href=https://github.com/hlais/Kata---a---Day><b>Back to README</b><a>

Day #55: 

Difficulty: 6 kyu

Solved: Monday, March 5th, 2018

Description:

Given a string of words, you need to find the highest scoring word.

Each letter of a word scores points according to it's position in the alphabet: a = 1, b = 2, c = 3 etc.

You need to return the highest scoring word as a string.

If two words score the same, return the word that appears earliest in the original string.

All letters will be lowercase and all inputs will be valid.